www.pendev.me / github.com/PatrykErNowak

Patryk Ernest Nowak

Frontend Developer

- © +48 791-586-632
- patryk.ernest.nowak@gmail.com
- (2) Lublin/Warszawa/remote



ABOUT ME

I am a self-taught programmer who has been interested in technology and computers from a young age. I have been programming and creating websites for two years.

Independence, persistence and patience are the features of my personality. My goal is to achieve an expert level by continuously improving my skills and keeping up with industry best practices.

SKILLS

HTML/CSS · JavaScript (ES6) · TypeScript

React (React Router • React/TanStack Query • Context API • Redux Toolkit • React Hook Form)

Jest/Vitest & React Testing Library

SASS/SCSS (with BEM) • TailwindCSS • CSS Modules • Styled Components

 ${\it AI/LLM/LangChain.js} \, \cdot \, {\it SQL} \, \cdot \, {\it Vite.js} \, \cdot \, {\it Gulp.js} \, \cdot \, {\it Parcel.js} \, \cdot \, {\it GIT/GITHUB} \, \cdot \, {\it Postman} \, \cdot \, {\it Docker}$

Mobile First • RWD • Ally • 3RD PARTY LIBRARIES (Axios, Swiper, AOS, Moment etc.)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance 02/2023 - Present

Frontend Developer

- · Create visually appealing and responsive user interfaces.
- Implement best practices for efficient rendering and resource utilization.
- Implement interactive features and dynamic behavior using JavaScript.
- · Test and ensure that web applications work seamlessly across various browsers and platforms.
- Use version control systems like Git to manage and track changes in codebase.

Projects See more projects on www.pendev.me/#myworks

BeFit Tracker app www.befittracker.netlify.app

Github repo

TypeScript React React Query React Router React Hook Form Supabase Vite.js A11Y

SPA that allows you to conveniently count calories and macronutrients, track physical activity and compare results. App designed and developed was with React (Peact Query for handle remark).

compare results. App designed and developed was with **React (React Query** for handle remote state, **React Router** for routing and **React Hook Form** for handle forms), additionally for styling i used **Styled Components**. To handle auth and store data i used **Supabase**.

M-Data www.m-data.me

TypeScript SCSS BEM Parcel.js Swiper.js AllY OOP MVC

Individual project - **SPA** Portfolio dedicated to Data Analyst. The main objective was to present the analyst's biography, skills and Power BI reports. My wholly designed and developed site was implemented with **Object-Oriented Programming** approach and **Model-View-Controller Pattern**. To build it, I used **Parcel.js**.

Frontend Mentor Challenges CHECK LIVE SITE

HTML/CSS/JS TypeScript React SCSS TailwindCSS CSS Modules Vite.js API

Here you can find a showcase of my front-end skills, where I try to practice the technical skills I have gathered. This collection features my solutions to various Frontend Mentor challenges, each providing a real-life workflow experience. From designs, assets, and style requirements. All solutions are created by me based on my knowledge.

DB Schenker/central team 05/2021 - 09/2023

Logistics specialist

- Support, coordination and control of the work of branches in Poland on the implementation of business processes and preparation.
- Analysis of statements, procedures and reports.
- Collaborating with the wider analyst team to deliver optimized business solutions.
- Participating in international business project to align of the implemented software with current business standards.
- · Testing mobile, web and desktop applications.

EDUCATION

UMCS in Lublin

Caracter Logistics

2016-2021

UP in Lublin

Dietetics

Dietetics 2013-2016

UMCS in Lublin

Computer Science

2011-2012

LANGUAGES

Polish Native English B2

STRENGTHS

Eager to learn new skills

As a person who is starting out, I am constantly seeking for new ways to grow and expand my skill set.

Not afraid of failure

Strong believer in the mantra that we learn from our mistakes.

Time management

I always set aside time to plan my week and distribute the workload by days so that I can simultaneously meet deadliness and maintain my well-being.

Problem Solving

Applied strong problem-solving skills in designing usable, aesthetically pleasing interfaces, leading to increased user engagement.

HOBBIES

FI motor sports snowboarding & skiing board games technology trends